Episode 1
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the scene?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage, have the
courage to sail and believe.
And we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow?
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons.
Sailed toward different dreams,
things have changed now!
For together we found, we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the conscious points our destiny!
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me.
Bon voyage, we can't stop all
our troubles, forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile?
We know we'll get there.
No regrets.
Every tear that we've cried only helps.
Our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Following Shura's vicious
defeat at the hands of Wiper,
only 80 now remained in the survival game.
Of the upper yard, perhaps
they lacked divine protection.
As the four members of Luffy's exploration
team know precisely the
location of the gold,
this island has kept secret for 400 years,
they set their sights on
it and head south from the
sacrificial altar. South.
I mean, straight up.
Directly south, or down opposite
of north, or, uh, whatever.
Sounds like the island is
having its fair share of drama.
I bet these homes were
built so far out from the
city in the hopes of greater
longevity with crops.
But it looks like all All this brush
swallowed up the mortar and brick.
I hope the city's still there.
What are you doing here, woman?
You should be aware that this
is a path to God's shrine.
Proceeding any further would be insolent.
Would you get down?
Do you even have a clue as to the
archeological significance of these ruins?
They're priceless.
How dare you talk back?
What are you doing here anyway?
You have some kind of business with me?
Yes, simple business, actually.
I've been charged by God
to eliminate any Shandians
or Blue Sea people I
find with my axe dial.
C 'est fleur.
And with a twist.
Such a lack of respect
Shandians!
Divine warriors!
I would've been better off
being alive at the altar!
And you call yourself Divine.
These guys are gonna be the end of us.
So far, they've managed to kill a
lot more of us than we have of them.
Sal should be to the right, so if I
keep to the right, I should find it.
That's one of those blue sea
people Wiper was talking about.
Gotta go take him out.
A gorilla.
And he looks pissed.
Die!
What's your problem?
You fellas have some serious
anger management issues.
Please, no.
I surrender.
I give up. I lose. You win.
Just, please, don't kill me. I won't.
Not again.
Listen, nutcase.
If you're not a priest, then
go find another goat to shoot.
I'm in a hurry here.
all right what's the
deal with these glowing
pistols no where'd it go
couldn't have gotten far
You put up a good fight.
I'm almost sorry I underestimated you.
Well, thanks, pal.
But I should apologize to you.
I took you for a loser.
He never moved his feet!
Hagia said there were different
types of dials up here.
I wonder if this guy has one
or two stuck to his shoes.
Because when he moves gusts of wind shoot
from his feet what else
could it be and those
pistols of his flash as bright as the sun
blinding me every time
he fires where is he now?
He's using all three?
Aren't you a hot shot?
Huh, this blue sea idiot has
no clue about using dials.
He doesn't even stand a chance.
Hey, guess what this is?
Oh no, it's called a milky dial.
You know, aerial combat isn't just
leaping around out of desperation.
That looks big!
A ton of wood in these things
would make for a killer barbecue.
That was stupid what's wrong with
me this guy's already faster than
me and i hang myself out like an
easy target oh and i got a bullet
in my leg genius gotta be something
i could do about the flashing
pistols hold on those guns of yours
are some pretty nice accessories
but too bad for you i
found my lucky goggles
which means your little
blinding trick won't work
on me anymore you might
as well give up those
just look like regular
goggles not a big fan of my
flash guns are you being
a swordsman you need
close quarters to fight
which i won't give you i
don't understand your
reasons for being here and
i don't care but i will
say that your mere presence
defines you as an enemy
of the Shandians now
i'm telling you surrender
or die which might
happen sooner if we keep
standing here that leg
of yours isn't getting any
better doesn't hurt too
bad barely made a dent
getting shot while i
made smug comments about
some big dead eel proves
i'm lacking in concentration
all right guess i
found the perfect situation
to test that technique.
again.
Let's give it a try.
Think you can run away?
Sight, sound, smell,
taste, touch, and thought.
These six roots ground us all
by way of good, evil, and peace.
What are you talking about?
And of course, each of these
can either be pure or impure.
These are the 36 earthly desires.
Listen up, I have the barrel of a
cannon aimed directly at your head!
Then all you have are a couple of pistols.
In both distance and power,
my weapon's superior.
You've done very well, but
you're still gonna die.
What can?
You're out of your mind.
All I see are three swords.
Have you ever seen a flying blade attack?
Attack this!
Single-sword style.
36-caliber Phoenix!
Comfortable.
Nothing personal being
natural enemies and all.
But you're in the dirt because
I hate being told what to do.
No other reason.
I'll survive.
You watch.
Where am I?
I've lost all sense of direction.
The trees are too tall for
me to see the sun. Help!
Please, Saru, I'll rub it. Please find me.
I don't want to be left
on this stinking island
is to die and turn into
food for gigantic bugs?
And if I do die, will there
even be a doctor waiting for me?
Wait, it doesn't matter.
When you're dead, you're dead,
and no doctor can save you.
But I don't want to die!
Now it's time for this awful
place thinking about deaths
and doctors and wondering why
couldn't I be something else?
Look at Dennis.
Dennis would be nice and hold people's
teeth and make them feel better.
No giant sky sharks and winged
people trying to kill me.
They still got my stick.
Wait, maybe I've already
died and gone to heaven.
These look like ruins.
We were supposed to meet at ruins.
Maybe they're already here waiting for me.
Or maybe I was so fast I beat them.
I'm so impressed with my
street navigational skills.
They led me to just the right place.
This is awesome.
I'm right.
I'm the first one here.
A raccoon dog.
I can do this all day if
you want, but you can't win.
Rifles and cannons won't
leave a scratch on me.
Rubber body and all.
So it would seem.
Time for a change of tactics.
This weapon is called the burn bazooka.
By igniting the gas released
from the breath dial,
a deadly blue flame is created which will
incinerate anything in its path instantly.
Let's see if you can
bounce this back at me.
What the heck is that thing?
It burned right through that giant tree.
Where'd it go?
Romp! Romp!
Let's go!
Romp!
Step!
That was close!
Come on, Tom!
Spear!
Do you like bazookas, huh?
Get a load of things!
Now you die!
Come, come!
Burn!
Bazooka!
That bastard's dead.
Sanchi!
Sanji?
No, Sanji. Get up, please.
This is bad. This is really bad. Sanji!
I can't even hear his heart beating.
It can't be.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
What a foolishly angry man.
If I'd come here today and brought
with me pain and destruction,
it would have been the
first thing you felt.
Then why are you here, Anaru?
Ha ha ha!
I expected a warmer hello.
It has been six years now,
my former god. Gonefall.
Thank you.